<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="pc_software_cat_item">
    <pc_software_cat_item action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <access_type>restricted</access_type>
        <active>true</active>
        <auto_created>false</auto_created>
        <availability>on_desktop</availability>
        <billable>false</billable>
        <category display_value="">7be1ba0d071121102016f9fc7c1ed0be</category>
        <checked_out/>
        <cost>0</cost>
        <custom_cart/>
        <delivery_plan display_value="DEFAULT">523da512c611228900811a37c97c2014</delivery_plan>
        <delivery_plan_script/>
        <delivery_time>1970-01-03 00:00:00</delivery_time>
        <description><![CDATA[Humans perceive the three-dimensional structure of the world with apparent ease. However, despite all of the recent advances in computer vision research, the dream of having a computer interpret an image at the same level as a two-year old remains elusive. Why is computer vision such a challenging problem and what is the current state of the art? Computer Vision: Algorithms and Applications explores the variety of techniques commonly used to analyze and interpret images. It also describes challenging real-world applications where vision is being successfully used, both for specialized applications such as medical imaging, and for fun, consumer-level tasks such as image editing and stitching, which students can apply to their own personal photos and videos. More than just a source of “recipes,” this exceptionally authoritative and comprehensive textbook/reference also takes a scientific approach to basic vision problems, formulating physical models of the imaging process before inverting them to produce descriptions of a scene. These problems are also analyzed using statistical models and solved using rigorous engineering techniques Topics and features: structured to support active curricula and project-oriented courses, with tips in the Introduction for using the book in a variety of customized courses; presents exercises at the end of each chapter with a heavy emphasis on testing algorithms and containing numerous suggestions for small mid-term projects; provides additional material and more detailed mathematical topics in the Appendices, which cover linear algebra, numerical techniques, and Bayesian estimation theory; suggests additional reading at the end of each chapter, including the latest research in each sub-field, in addition to a full Bibliography at the end of the book; supplies supplementary course material for students at the associated website, http://szeliski.org/Book/. Suitable for an upper-level undergraduate or graduate-level course in computer science or engineering, this textbook focuses on basic techniques that work under real-world conditions and encourages students to push their creative boundaries. Its design and exposition also make it eminently suitable as a unique reference to the fundamental techniques and current research literature in computer vision.]]></description>
        <display_price_property>non_zero</display_price_property>
        <entitlement_script/>
        <features/>
        <flow_designer_flow/>
        <fulfillment_automation_level>unspecified</fulfillment_automation_level>
        <group/>
        <hide_sp>false</hide_sp>
        <icon/>
        <ignore_price>false</ignore_price>
        <image/>
        <location/>
        <mandatory_attachment>false</mandatory_attachment>
        <meta/>
        <mobile_hide_price>false</mobile_hide_price>
        <mobile_picture/>
        <mobile_picture_type>use_desktop_picture</mobile_picture_type>
        <model/>
        <name/>
        <no_attachment_v2>true</no_attachment_v2>
        <no_cart>false</no_cart>
        <no_cart_v2>false</no_cart_v2>
        <no_delivery_time_v2>false</no_delivery_time_v2>
        <no_order>false</no_order>
        <no_order_now>false</no_order_now>
        <no_proceed_checkout>false</no_proceed_checkout>
        <no_quantity>false</no_quantity>
        <no_quantity_v2>true</no_quantity_v2>
        <no_search>false</no_search>
        <no_wishlist_v2>false</no_wishlist_v2>
        <omit_price>false</omit_price>
        <order>0</order>
        <ordered_item_link/>
        <owner display_value="System Administrator">6816f79cc0a8016401c5a33be04be441</owner>
        <picture/>
        <preview>JavaScript: popupOpenStandard("com.glideapp.servicecatalog_cat_item_view.do?v=1&amp;sysparm_id=ff2bfc4307d721102016f9fc7c1ed0fb&amp;sysparm_preview=true", "summary");</preview>
        <product_id/>
        <published_ref/>
        <recurring_frequency/>
        <request_method/>
        <roles/>
        <sc_catalogs>7472d5de075321102016f9fc7c1ed03c</sc_catalogs>
        <sc_ic_item_staging/>
        <sc_ic_version/>
        <sc_template/>
        <short_description>Computer Vision: Algorithms and Applicat</short_description>
        <show_variable_help_on_load>false</show_variable_help_on_load>
        <specs/>
        <start_closed>false</start_closed>
        <state/>
        <sys_class_name>pc_software_cat_item</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2023-06-12 13:29:47</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>ff2bfc4307d721102016f9fc7c1ed0fb</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name/>
        <sys_package display_value="Library" source="x_976190_library">5812a33f0701e1102016f9fc7c1ed031</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Library">5812a33f0701e1102016f9fc7c1ed031</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>pc_software_cat_item_ff2bfc4307d721102016f9fc7c1ed0fb</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2023-06-12 13:29:47</sys_updated_on>
        <taxonomy_topic/>
        <template/>
        <template_manager_roles/>
        <type>item</type>
        <u_catalog_item/>
        <u_library_catalog/>
        <upc/>
        <use_sc_layout>true</use_sc_layout>
        <vendor/>
        <vendor_catalog_item/>
        <visible_bundle>true</visible_bundle>
        <visible_guide>true</visible_guide>
        <visible_standalone>true</visible_standalone>
        <workflow/>
    </pc_software_cat_item>
    <sys_translated_text action="delete_multiple" query="documentkey=ff2bfc4307d721102016f9fc7c1ed0fb"/>
    <fx_price action="delete_multiple" query="id=ff2bfc4307d721102016f9fc7c1ed0fb"/>
</record_update>
